你们想好点啥菜了吗
Hey, you guys ready to order?
-想好了  -好的  普丽娅
- Uh, sure. - Okay, Priya?
我来一份肉馅土豆泥饼
Uh, I'll have the shepherd's pie.
你想和我分着吃一份吗
You want to split that with me?
别别别  他不会愿意的
Oh, no, no, no, he doesn't.
为啥
Why not?
土豆泥里面有牛奶
Well, you have milk in the taters,
肉汁里面有牛奶  还有帕尔玛干酪饼皮
milk in the gravy, parmesan crust.
你这位乳糖不耐的男朋友会变成
Your lactose-intolerant boyfriend will turn
一个充气的感恩节大气球
into a gas-filled Macy's Day balloon.
你说的不全对
Not quite accurate.
感恩节气球里充的都是氦气
The Macy's balloons are filled with helium,
而莱纳德肚子里造出来的是大量的甲烷
whereas Leonard produces copious amounts of methane.
所以  还是别点肉馅土豆泥饼了
So, no, on the shepherd's pie.
能接着点菜吗
Can we move on?
行  再给一条小贴士  他说自己能吃冻酸奶
Yeah, a little tip: he says he can eat frozen yogurt.
千万别信
Do not believe it.
海鲈  我想来份海鲈
Sea bass! I'll have the sea bass!
你得习惯啊
You gotta like this,
现任女友和前任女友通过
the girlfriend and the ex-girlfriend bonding
聊你的糗事来联络感情
over your rooty-tooty stinky booty.
杀了我吧
Kill me.
没用的  人体能在死亡数小时内
It wouldn't help. The human body is capable
一直制造气体
of being flatulent for hours after death.
各位  抱歉来晚了
Guys, sorry I'm late.
我有个好消息
I have amazing news.
伯纳黛特  在你换话题之前
Bernadette, before you change the subject,
有人想对莱纳德糟糕的消化系统
does anyone have any final comments on
来个终极吐槽吗
Leonard's faulty digestive system?
啥好消息啊  伯纳黛特
So, what's your news, Bernadette?
论文委员会接受了我的博士论文
The thesis committee accepted my doctoral dissertation.
我拿到博士学位了
I'm getting my PhD!
哇  恭喜恭喜
Wow! Oh, congratulations.
哇  这就意味着你是博士  你是博士
Wow, so that means you're a doctor, you're a doctor,
你也是博士  你还是博士
you're a doctor, you're a doctor,
而霍华德  你认识不少博士啊
and Howard, you know a lot of doctors.
祝贺你呀  亲爱的
Congratulations, honey.
谢谢
Thank you.
霍华德  跟我们说说当你得知
So, Howard, tell us, how's it feel knowing
等你俩结婚了  大家得叫你们
that when you two get married,
沃罗威茨先生和沃罗威茨博士  你作何感想
you'll be referred to as Mr. and Dr. Wolowitz?
除非他能随伯纳黛特的姓
Unless he takes Bernadette's last name.
考虑到伯纳黛特的地位更高
And considering her advanced status,
这么做未尝不可
that could open some doors for him.
拜托  今天的主角不是我
Please, this isn't about me.
我真为你骄傲
I'm proud of you.
还有更让你骄傲的呢
Well, you'll be really be proud of this.
我被一家大型医药公司看中了
I was headhunted by a big pharmaceutical company.
他们要给我提供巨额薪金
They're gonna pay me a buttload of money!
什么
What?
伯纳黛特  这太好了
Bernadette, that's great.
霍华德  你能挣巨额的钱吗
Howard, do you make a buttload?
反正比你放巨额的屁强
Better than what you've got a buttload of.
喂  要是我摇下车窗玻璃  一切都还是很美好的
Hey, if I roll down the windows in the car, everything's peachy.
可如果你也这么做  你还是当不了博士
If you do it, you're still not a doctor.
嗯  车窗户这这句我得吐个槽
Yeah, just a heads-up on the car window deal.
虽然说得对  但不是每件事都那么美好
It helps, but everything is not "peachy."
生活大爆炸第四季第二十四集[本季终]
*如果你有问题  你又不能解决*
*Oh, if there was a problem, you can't solve it*
嘻哈歌曲《Ice Ice baby》
*接受这诱惑  让我的DJ来解决*
*Check out the hook while my DJ revolves it*
*冰  冰  宝贝*
*Ice, Ice, baby*
天啊  我觉得穿着这件衣服显得好傻啊
Oh, God, I feel ridiculous in this dress.
你看起来美极了  乌胡拉少尉
You look beautiful, Lieutenant Uhura.
那现在开始准备  检查
Now prepare for... inspection.
嘘  别让我哥听见了
Shh, my brother's going to hear you.
放心吧  他带着耳机呢
Relax, he's got headphones on.
而我们正在距地球16公里远的星际飞船里呢
And we're ten miles above Earth in a starship.
开玩笑吧  才16公里
Really, ten miles?
还在大气层里转悠啊
You're orbiting inside the atmosphere?
地球大气的平均厚度约为1000公里
脑残
Moron.
我真不敢相信我在穿我哥的万圣节化妆服
I can't believe I'm wearing my brother's Halloween costume.
我真不敢相信你真以为他只在万圣节的时候穿
I can't believe you think he only wears it on Halloween.
打开"降落舱门"  "航天飞机"正在进入
Open the landing bay doors, shuttle craft approaching.
好吧  我得撤了
Okay, gotta go.
嗨  怎么了
Hey, what's up?
是我未来的儿媳博士来了吗
Is that my future daughter-in-law, the doctor?!
不是  妈  是拉杰
No, Ma! It's Raj!
-他也是博士  对吗  -对
- He's a doctor too, right?! - Yes!
跟莱纳德和那个竹竿子一样
Like Leonard and the skinny weirdo!
那是谢尔顿  没错
Sheldon, yes!
除了我  大家都是博士
Everybody's a doctor but me!
那能怪谁呢
Well, whose fault is that?!
怎么了
What's up?
莱纳德在我的记忆海绵床垫上
Leonard's putting disgusting memories in
制造恶心的记忆
my memory foam mattress.
我今晚能睡你这儿吗
Can I stay here tonight?
行  但我要去见伯纳黛特
Sure, but I'm going out with Bernadette.
所以就你和我妈在家
It'll just be you and my mother.
我猜应该没事吧
I guess that's okay.
妈  拉杰能睡这儿吗
Ma, can Rajesh sleep over?!
行啊  他可以和我玩扮医生的游戏[doctor也有医生的意思]
Of course, he and I can play doctor!
她在开玩笑  对吧
She's kidding, right?
我不知道  自从接受荷尔蒙替换治疗之后
I don't know, she's pretty feisty since
她就变得精力充沛了
they put her on hormone-replacement therapy.
呼叫小可爱医生
Paging Dr. Cutie Pie!
我不得不说  艾米  我对于
I must say, Amy, I was very impressed
伯纳黛特拿到博士学位感到非常惊讶
to see that Bernadette got her PhD.
确实令人钦佩
It's indeed admirable.
虽然  她是搞  微生物学的
Although, it is... microbiology.
你的博士学位是神经生物学的
Your doctorate is in neurobiology.
我看不出什么差别
I fail to see the distinction.
我就这么跟你说吧
I'll make it simple for you.
我研究的是大脑
I study the brain,
这是能让贝多芬写出《命运交响曲》的器官
the organ responsible for Beethoven's Fifth Symphony.
而伯纳黛特研究的是酵母菌
Bernadette studies yeast,
是用来制造Michelob Lite啤酒的有机体
the organism responsible for Michelob Lite.
你的脖子不舒服吗
Is there something wrong with your neck?
有点僵硬
It's a little stiff.
如此不堪一击的结构
What a remarkably fragile structure
却要支撑如此价值连城的设备
to support such a valuable payload.
这无异于用精灵粉末糖来支撑皇室珠宝彩蛋
Not unlike balancing a Faberge egg on a Pixie Stick.
你考虑过做个按摩吗
Have you considered massage?
我想用讽刺的口吻来回答你的问题
I'd like to respond to that sarcastically:
是的  让一个陌生人给我的身体涂油并按压
Yes, I relish the thought of a stranger covering my body
这个想法很不错
with oil and rubbing it.
我是建议你亲手对自己的肌肉进行按摩
I was proposing you massage your muscles with your own hands.
那还是会涉及到很多不必要的触碰
Still sounds like a lot of unnecessary touching.
相信我
Trust me.
伸出你的右手
With your right hand,
找到肩胛骨和肩峰的交界处
locate the spot where the scapula meets the acromion process.
好了
All right.
然后用右手中指沿肩胛的突起进行按压
Now push your third finger along the ridge of the shoulder blade,
同时小幅度揉动
making a small rotation as you do so.
揉着呢
Rotating.
你应该能感觉到有一个突起的结构
You should feel a small node-like object
在沿着骨头前后滚动
rolling back and forth along the bone.
你是指肌筋膜点吗
You mean the myofascial point?
不然呢
Obviously.
接着向其施力
Now bear down on it
就像我们熟悉的七年级生
like the seventh grade noogies
欺负人用的经典按头动作
we all know too well.
额滴神啊  爽  爽  爽
Oh, dear Lord, yes, yes, oh, yes!
艾米  以前从来没人这么摸过我
Amy, I've never been touched like this before!
我的手简直是神来之手啊
Oh! My hands are magic!
别自吹自擂了
Don't flatter yourself.
你的手不过是在本人神经系统知识指导下的
Your hands are blunt tools guided by my knowledge
一个愚钝的工具而已
of the nervous system.
我刚也可以轻易地让你瘫痪
I could just as easily have paralyzed you.
有人在敲门
There's someone at my door.
我对此不感兴趣  拜拜
That doesn't interest me. Good-bye.
-我能在这里过夜吗  -凭什么
- Can I sleep here tonight? - Why?
莱纳德正和我妹妹进行星际迷航式的性交
Leonard's having astronomically inaccurate
那从天文学角度来说很不科学
Star Trek sex with my sister.
的确很令人心烦意乱  进来吧
I can see how that would be upsetting. Come in.
我去拿铺在沙发上的床单和毯子
I'll get the sheets and blankets for the couch.
不用了  我去莱纳德的房间睡就行
Oh, don't bother. I'll just sleep in Leonard's room.
不行  我不能授权
No, I can't authorize that.
他能睡在我床上  我为啥不能睡在他床上
Well, he's in my bed. Why can't I be in his?
汉谟拉比法典上规定可以"以眼还眼"
The Hammurabic Code is "an eye for an eye,"
而并非"以床还床"
not "a bed for a bed."
行行好  哥们  我快累死了
Come on, dude, I'm exhausted,
提拉·班克斯说过
and Tyra Banks says
提拉·班克斯  美国著名模特
化妆包里最重要的一样东西
the most important item in your makeup bag
就是夜晚香甜的睡眠
is a good night's sleep.
好吧
All right.
要想使用"莱纳德的卧室"
This is a form indemnifying me
需要先签署这张我的免责表
from your use of "Leonard's bedroom."
在这里签字  说明我试图阻止过你
Sign here, indicating that I tried to stop you
并摆出过严厉的面部表情
and did so using a stern facial expression.
-晚安  谢尔顿  -等等  还没完
- Good night, Sheldon.  - Wait. Not yet.
我们还要重温一下安全规程
We still have to go over safety procedures.
这间公寓里共有三个紧急出口  分别在
Now, the apartment has three emergency exits located
这里  这里和这里
here, here, and here.
万一遇到停电事故
In the event of a power outage,
夜光漆可指引你从最近的出口逃生
luminous paint will guide you to the nearest exit.
开玩笑吧你
You're kidding.
在安全问题上  我从不儿戏
I never kid about safety.
你在我房间里干什么
What are you doing here?
睡觉啊
I was sleeping.
在我床上
In my bed?
我也想睡在自己的床上
Well, I would've slept in my own bed,
但它却用来给我的家庭带来耻辱
but it was being used to bring shame to my family.
吉恩·罗登贝瑞  《星际迷航》中的演员
还让我想起来了吉恩·罗登贝瑞
And the memory of Gene Roddenberry.
你听见了吗
Oh, you heard?
"史考特  我需要更多的能量"
"Scotty, I need more power."
抱歉  谢尔顿知道你睡在这里吗
Sorry. Does Sheldon know you're sleeping in here?
怎么可能不知道  他逼我签了免责书
Are you kidding? He made me sign a waiver,
参加了紧急消防演习
participate in an emergency fire drill
还复习了心脏复苏术的课程
and take a refresher course in CPR.
还好他有个人体模型
Thank God he had a dummy.
是啊  嘴对嘴的莫娜
Oh, yeah. Mouth-to-Mouth Mona.
知道吗  她和霍华德谈过恋爱
You know, she used to date Howard?
天啊  她就是那个莫娜吗
Oh, my God, she's that Mona?
你和我妹妹为什么不能在这里共度春宵呢
Why can't you and my sister spend your nights here?
我们试过  但是她和谢尔顿合不来
We tried. She doesn't get along with Sheldon.
谢尔顿跟他自己都合不来
Sheldon doesn't get along with Sheldon.
但那也不足以说服我听你的话
It's still no reason for me to have to listen to you
每晚都要装备上光子鱼雷
arm your photon torpedoes every night.
好吧  不如这样
Okay, well, how about this:
在普丽娅找到自己的住处之前
until Priya gets her own place,
你住在这里  而我住在你家
you stay here and I'll stay at your apartment.
我能带女孩过来吗
Can I bring girls here?
就凭你
You?
当然了  想带多少带多少
Sure. Bring as many as you want.
好的  就这么定了
Okay, deal.
别强迫她们就行了
Just not against their will.
你觉得吃那块蛋糕合适吗
You really think you should be eating that cake?
怎么了
Why?
鉴于你即将成为富婆的小白脸老公
If you're gonna be a trophy husband for a rich wife,
你可要注意自己的腰围啊
you might want to watch your waistline.
他说得对
He's right.
嘴上一时享受  臀上一世肥肉
A minute on the lips, a lifetime on the hips.
是啊  真幽默
Yeah, ha-ha.
首先  我未婚妻的成功并没对我造成威胁
First of all, I'm not threatened by my fiance's success.
我为她感到骄傲
I'm proud of her.
其次  我拥有自己的事业
And secondly, I have my own career.
有了孩子可就不一样了
Until you have kids.
好消息  拉杰
Good news, Raj.
我刚从实验室取回了你的血样报告
I got the blood work back from the lab.
你可以在我家待上一段时间了
You're okay to stay for a while.
你什么时候帮我抽的血
When did you take my blood?
这不重要
Not important.
你血糖有点偏高
Your sugar was a little high.
我会跟你医生保持联系的
I'd follow up with your regular physician.
同时  这里还有些文件
In the meantime, I have some paperwork here
要请你过目
for you to go over.
这又是什么东东
What the hell is this?
都是些陈辞滥调啦
Boilerplate stuff.
针对临时住客的改良版室友协议
A modified roommate agreement for a temporary house guest.
还有生前遗嘱和永久委托书
And a living will and durable power of attorney.
这里说你可以帮我决定生命终止与否
This says you can make "end of life" decisions for me.
作为朋友  希望事不至此
As your friend, let's hope it doesn't come to that.
签名吧
Please sign.
你签过这个吗
Did you sign this?
上面有互惠条款
There's a reciprocity clause.
你也可以终结他的
You get to pull the plug on him, too.
好吧  这样挺公平
Well, that seems fair.
恭喜了  欢迎暂时入住
Congratulations and welcome temporarily aboard.
这是你的ID卡
Here's your I.D. card,
钥匙和胸牌
your key and your lapel pin.
莱纳德居然觉得这胸牌配不上他
Which Leonard was too cool to wear.
还有  作为临时室友的部分职责
FYI, part of your responsibilities as roommate pro tem
是送我上下班
will be to drive me to and from work,
送我去漫画书店  理发店
the comic book store, the barbershop
隔周周日送我去公园呼吸新鲜空气
and the park for one hour every other Sunday for fresh air.
带上个球或飞盘
Bring a ball or a Frisbee,
好让他去接
you know, something he can chase.
还有  所有的外卖都由你负责帮我带
Also, you're tasked with bringing home all takeout dinners.
今晚是泰国菜
Tonight is Thai food.
标准点菜订单在附录B
You'll find the standard order in appendix B
或可从我的FTP下载
or downloadable from my FTP server.
如有任何问题
If you have any questions,
这里列出了常见问题的答案
here's the FAQ sheet,
若你更喜欢人性化解答
or if you prefer the human touch,
每周四晚我提供公寓问题的在线聊天服务
I do a live web chat called "Apartment Talk" on Tuesday nights
不许反悔哦
No backsies.
谢尔顿  吃晚餐了
Sheldon, dinner!
这是什么
What is this?
这就是单纯吃饭与用餐的区别
This is the difference between eating and dining.
太了不起了  我这才意识到
Remarkable. I'm just realizing how much
莱纳德这么些年一直有多敷衍
Leonard's been skating by all these years.
没什么大不了的
It's not a big thing.
就把我看成棕色版的玛莎·斯图尔特吧
Just think of me as a brown Martha Stewart.
玛莎·斯图尔特  美国家政女王  主妇界的偶像
嗨  谢尔顿
Hey, Sheldon,
你是不是又改了无线上网密码
did you change your Wi-Fi password again?
对  现在是"佩妮自己去开无线上网"  没有空格
Yes, it's "Penny, get your own Wi-Fi." No spaces.
多谢
Thanks.
这一大桌好料是怎么回事
What's with the fancy spread?
这是我的新室友在不遗余力地
My new roommate is bending over backwards
迎合讨好我
to ingratiate himself to me.
顺便说  胸牌别的好
Uh, nice touch, by the way.
什么"新室友"  莱纳德怎么了
What do you mean "new roommate"? What happened to Leonard?
跟直立人一样
The same thing that happened to Homo erectus.
被更高级物种取代了
He was replaced by a superior species.
我是这家新新人[我是新的同性恋]
I'm the new Homo in town.
那是口误
That came out wrong.
好吧  这么问吧  莱纳德在哪
All right, let me try this again. Where's Leonard?
他住在我公寓  所以我住这来了
He's living at my place, so I'm living here.
你目前只是暂时住这
You're living here provisionally.
但我必须说  你干得不错
But I must say it's looking good.
莱纳德和普丽娅同居了
Leonard and Priya are living together?
这可是大事啊
That's big.
不  手工折的餐巾天鹅
No. Origami napkin swans...
这才是大事
that's the headline.
而且是好事
It's a good thing.
你知道在这个制药厂  你将从事
So do you know what kind of research you'll be doing
哪方面的研究吗
at this pharmaceutical company?
有很多种选择
Well, there are a couple of opportunities available,
但我自愿参加了早泄问题研究
but I volunteered for the premature ejaculation project.
反正我们俩都没有心脏病
I mean, it's not like either one of us has heart disease.
差点忘了  我给你买了个小礼物
Oh, I almost forgot. I got you a little present.
妮妮  你不用这样的
Oh, Bernie, no. You didn't have to.
我想给你买嘛  来  打开看看
I wanted to. Come on, open it.
你给我买了块劳力士手表
You bought me a Rolex?
这得多少钱啊
How much did this cost?
让我来操心赚钱的事吧
Oh, you let me worry about the money.
我只想我的宝贝拥有漂亮东西
I just want my baby to have pretty things.
再来点酒吗
More wine?
不不不  我已经高了
Oh, no, no, no. I've had way too much already.
关于酒  有个很有趣的事...
Here's an interesting fact about alcohol...
再给我满上
Hit me.
人类并不是唯一一个
Man is not the only species
会发酵水果酿酒的物种
that ferments fruit in order to become intoxicated.
能猜到还有哪个物种也会吗
Can you guess what the other is?
提示  有时他们会把酒装进旅行箱[trunk也有象鼻的意思]
Hint: sometimes they pack the alcohol in their trunks.
猴子
Monkeys.
猴子什么时候有旅行箱了
When does a monkey have a trunk?
当手提箱太小装不下酒时
When a suitcase just won't do.
好吧
Mmm, all right.
很快就知道酒精是不是
It would appear as if alcohol
正在将你的智力一步步夺走
is playing keep-away with your intelligence.
晚安
Good night.
请记住  已经10点多了
Please note, it is now past 10:00 p.m.
根据我们的室友协议  请好心避免
Per our roommate agreement, kindly refrain
刺耳的笑声
from raucous laughter,
玻璃的叮当声和庆祝的炮火声
clinking of glasses, and celebratory gunfire.
好吧
Okay...
请教一下
explain something to me.
你眼睁睁看着莱纳德忍受他一年又一年
You watch Leonard put up with that guy for years and years.
你脑子里哪根筋搭错  让你觉得
What has to break inside your brain for you to think,
"克利须那神  我也想被折磨一把"
"Oh, Krishna, I've got to get me some of that"?
这比在自家公寓
Well, it's a lot better than having
戴着消音耳机强多了
to wear noise-cancelling headphones in my own apartment.
什么  天啊  我懂我懂
What? Oh, God, yeah. Yeah.
莱纳德在床上是个吵死人的小混蛋
Leonard's a noisy little dude in the sack.
-夜夜笙歌  -真的吗
- Every night. - Really?
即使在接吻和喘气都得轮流干的
Even during allergy season, when he has to alternate
过敏季节也这样吗
between kissing and breathing?
那是我妹妹  咱们就此打住行吗
It's my sister. Can we not talk about this anymore?
好  抱歉抱歉
Yeah. Sorry, sorry.
我能告诉你个秘密吗
Can I tell you a secret?
行
Yeah.
是我搞砸了
I screwed up.
莱纳德是个好人
Leonard's a great guy.
我不应该跟他分手的
Never should have broken up with him.
其实应该是来自Alfred Lord Tennyson
我改编一下莎士比亚的话好了
Well, uh, to paraphrase Shakespeare:
"爱过  失去过"
"It's better to have loved and lost
原话应该是It's better to have loved and lost than never to have loved at all.
"总好过每晚在家"
"than to stay home every night
"下载日益下流的黄色图片"
and download increasingly shameful pornography."
你个可怜的小家伙
Ohh... you poor baby.
我这是什么毛病  佩妮
What's wrong with me, Penny?
没病  没病
Nothing, nothing.
如果我们不是朋友
You know, if we weren't friends,
如果你没提到那个恶心黄色图片小故事的话
and you hadn't brought up that creepy pornography story,
我肯定会爬到你身上
I'd be on you like
以光速平方进出身体  产生能量
the speed of light squared on matter to make energy.
哇  你居然完全懂啊
Hey, you totally got that right!
能量等于质量乘以光速的平方[爱因斯坦质能等价理论]
"E=mc2."
我听着呢
I listen.
虽然不知道什么意思  但我听着呢
I have no idea what it means, but I listen.
-致友谊  -致友谊
- To friendship. - To friendship.
你们俩酒鬼能别发出那种讨人厌的碰杯声吗
Would you booze hounds please stop that infernal clinking?!
还有  答案是大象
And the answer was elephant!
莱纳德  亲爱的
Leonard, sweetheart,
我们是在接吻  不是在喝热汤
we're kissing, not eating hot soup.
抱歉
Sorry.
我父母要跟我视频通话
That's my parents on video chat.
快躲进卧室里
Go hide in the bedroom.
拜托
Oh, come on!
为什么不直接告诉他们  我们在约会呢
Why don't we just tell them that we're dating?
我们讨论过这个  现在还不是时候
Oh, we've been through this. It's not the time.
那何时才是时候
When is the time?
我有5个兄弟姐妹
I've got five brothers and sisters.
肯定会有其中一个闯大祸
One of them is bound to screw up real big,
到时候我就向我父母介绍你
and then I'll tell my parents about you.
-现在快闪  -好吧
- Now, shoo. - Fine.
你好  妈咪  你好  爹地
Hello, Mummy. Hello, Daddy.
我们听说堪萨斯城有龙卷风
We heard there was a tornado in Kansas City.
那离你们近吗
Is that close to you?
不近
No.
你哥哥呢
Where is your brother?
跟朋友出去玩了
Out with friends.
我不喜欢这样  一个年轻姑娘独自在家
I don't like it, a young girl alone in an apartment.
等你下个月搬回来后
I'll sleep so much better
我的睡眠质量肯定上升不少
when you move back here next month.
你要搬回印度
You're moving back to India?!
谁在那儿
Who's that?
天啊  你屋子里有别人
Oh, my God! There's someone in your apartment.
快打电话给美国的警察
Call the police in America!
你打算什么时候告诉我这事
When were you going to tell me about this?
你好啊  莱纳德
Oh, hello, Leonard.
真是个意外的惊喜啊
What a pleasant surprise!
妈咪爹地  你还记得拉杰的朋友莱纳德吧
Mummy, Daddy, you remember Rajesh's friend Leonard.
我以为你说拉杰跟朋友出去玩了
I thought you said Rajesh was out with his friends.
他有很多朋友  好不好
He has many friends.
拉杰居然有很多朋友
Rajesh has many friends?
你为什么要对我们撒谎
Why are you lying to us?
她撒谎是因为她不想告诉你们
She's lying because she doesn't want you to know
-我们在约会  -莱纳德
- we're dating. - Leonard!
现在还有什么区别吗
Well, what difference does it make?
如果你回印度  我们肯定是要分手的
If you're moving back to India, we're obviously breaking up.
那啥  我现在不想讨论这个问题
You know what? I don't want to deal with this right now.
所以说
So...
印度很热吧
Hot in India?
当然是  一直是  这可是印度
Of course it is. It always is. It's India.
现在你有什么好说的
Now, what do you have to say for yourself?
你们家的挂毯真漂亮
That is a beautiful tapestry.
天啊
Oh, God.
上帝啊
Oh, God!
你给我听着
Okay, look.
这事从没发生过
This never happened.
明白吗
Do you understand me?
搞毛啊  都这样了还不敢跟姐说话
Really?! Still can't talk to me?
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
什么
What?
我问  你在这儿干嘛
I said, what are you doing here?
我住这儿
I live here.
我的文件可不是这么说的
I have paperwork that says differently.
普丽娅要回印度了
Priya's going back to India.
这是两码事
Irrelevant.
拉杰和我相处得很融洽
Rajesh and I have a good thing going
你不能就这么毁掉它
and you're not going to ruin it.
你来这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
我一宿没睡
I've been up all night.
-我跟贝纳黛特吵了一架  -为什么
- I had a fight with Bernadette. - Why?
她送了我一块漂亮的手表
She gave me a beautiful watch.
莱纳德  你懂他在说啥吗
Leonard, do you understand this?
我懂
Yes.
跟他说去
Talk to him.
完了
Damn.
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
反正不是你们看上去的那样
It's-it's not what it looks like.
那到底看上去像怎么样
What does it look like?